mypict.me 2013-03-11

# UberMedia » Privacy Policy

UberMedia is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store and use information from and about users of our websites, including www.ubermedia.com, www.chime.in, www.ubersocial.com, and www.echofon.com (the “Sites”), and any services or software available or enabled via the Sites (“Services”). This Privacy Policy is subject to our [Universal Terms](http://ubermedia.com/all-terms/terms). By using our Sites or Services, you expressly consent to UberMedia’s collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with anything in this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Sites or the Services.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

  1. **Automatic Collection** : Like most other websites, we use common internet technologies such as _cookies_ and _Web beacons_ to keep track of users’ interactions with the Site and the Services. This may include your _internet protocol (IP) address, referring website addresses, browser type and access times_. A glossary that explains each of these italicized terms is included at the end of this Privacy Policy. If you use the Services, we may also collect data related to your use of the application and the device on which the application is loaded.
  2. **Volunteered** : If you register with us, fill out a profile page, purchase products or services, send us an email, or share personal information with us in any other way, we will collect and store whatever information you share. This obviously depends on what information you choose to provide but it may include your name, email address, credit card information or other billing information. You do not have to share this information with us, but without it you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in certain areas of the Site or Services.
  3. **Publicly Posted** : If you post information on public areas of the Site (or elsewhere on the internet), that information may be collected, stored and used by anyone, including us. (We strongly recommend that you do not post any information that allows strangers to identify or locate you. Posting such information may result in unsolicited messages or contact from others, to say the least.)
  4. **Use of Social Media Applications** : The Services utilize certain APIs, “feeds” or other mechanisms provided by third parties, including Twitter or Facebook as applicable (“Third Party Apps”), to access your accounts as authorized by you during your use of the Services and to display Content (as defined in our Terms) on your desktop or mobile device. The Third Party Apps work within the privacy settings of the account holders for such third party services and do not access Content, data or information not authorized by those privacy settings. Please refer to the privacy settings in your account to manage your public profile and other aspects of your account.
  5. **Mobile Location Information** : If you have activated a mobile application and permitted your mobile or other location-aware device to transmit location data, we will collect and store information related to your mobile device location to help provide a better experience with our Services. Some functional use of the Services may be dependent on the data related to your geographic location and geopositional data. If the settings on your location-aware device allow us to receive location information, we may also associate location information with other information we have about you.

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**

The short answer is that we use information to help us provide you with better experience with the Sites and Services. It also helps our advertisers and partners provide you with more relevant offers. Among other things, the information we collect enables UberMedia to: 

  * customize the advertising and content you see
  * fulfill your requests for products and services and validate your user rights
  * improve the Sites and Services
  * contact and communicate with you
  * conduct research and analysis
  * provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients
  * provide you with additional information we think is of interest to you

**WHEN DO WE SHARE OR DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION?**

  * **Anonymous Information.** Anonymous information is information that does not identify you personally, like your IP address and referring website addresses. We may share anonymous information with others, such as advertisers, sponsors and business partners.
  * **All Information (Both Anonymous and Personally Identifiable).** In certain circumstances, we may share any or all information we have collected, including personally identifiable information. For example: 
    * We might share your personally identifiable information during due diligence or in preparation for or after a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation.
    * If you give us permission, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties who might send you marketing and promotional information.
    * Your personal information may be transferred to anyone who is helping us make the Sites and Services available and functional, like technical agents, payment processing vendors, other subcontractors, and our affiliates and consultants.
    * As in any transaction, if you provide your credit card information to us for purchases, your credit card company will be provided with all relevant information about us, item(s) purchased, cost and other information necessary to process the transaction.
    * We may disclose your personal information if permitted or required by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend our interests or the interests of our users or business partners.

**CHILDREN UNDER 13**

The Sites is not intended for children under age 13, or for anyone under age 18 without involvement of a parent or guardian. The Sites includes unmonitored content posted by users and sourced from other third parties and as you can imagine, such content may be unsuitable for children. We do not knowingly collect or distribute information from or about children under 13.

**THIRD PARTIES**

  * Like most (maybe all) other websites, third parties may directly gather non-personally identifiable information from users of the Sites through automated means such as Cookies. For example, we may engage a third party to help us track and analyze anonymous information from users who visit the Sites or use the Services or the performance of advertisements. In addition, advertisers and ad-serving services may set Cookies or other automated mechanisms that gather anonymous information. This Privacy Policy does not cover how third parties use Cookies or other technologies or any information they gather through such technologies.
  * The Sites and Services may contain links to websites or other properties and content operated by third parties over which UberMedia has no control. Their privacy policies may be different from our Privacy Policy, and you access such linked websites or third-party content at your own risk.

**SECURITY**

Information that UberMedia collects is stored on servers that UberMedia manages, using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information. Please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet or information contained in our servers can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, UberMedia cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Sites or Services and you do so at your own risk.

**FOREIGN COUNTRIES**

Your personal information may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state or country or to a jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your location. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that UberMedia processes and stores information in the United States and your use of our Sites or Services constitutes your consent to and understanding of this processing.

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

UberMedia reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and will do so by posting changes to this Privacy Policy. The new Privacy Policy will apply to all current and past users of the Sites and will replace any prior Privacy Policies that are inconsistent. 

**DISPUTE RESOLUTION**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California applicable to agreements made and performed in California, excluding the application of the conflict of laws provisions. You agree that any action or suit brought by a party to enforce or adjudicate your rights under this Agreement shall be brought in the federal or state courts located in Los Angeles, California.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California applicable to agreements made and performed in California, excluding the application of the conflict of laws provisions. You agree that any action or suit brought by a party to enforce or adjudicate your rights under this Agreement shall be brought in the federal or state courts located in Los Angeles, California.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we have shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes in the past 12 months. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which such was shared. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: UberMedia, Inc.; Attn: Privacy Policy; 130 West Union Street; Pasadena, CA 91103. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or UberMedia’s privacy practices, please email us at [privacy@ubermedia.com](mailto:privacy@ubermedia.com).

Or you can contact us by mail at:

UberMedia, Inc.  
130 West Union Street  
Pasadena, CA 91103

In addition, if you wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing, or if you would like to update or delete your email address, mailing address or other personal information, or otherwise manage communications your receive from UberMedia, please contact us at the above.

Effective: July 1, 2012

**Glossary**

  * _Cookie:_ When you visit the Sites or utilize an UberMedia product or service, UberMedia’s servers send a cookie (a small file with a string of characters) to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you but they recognize your individual web browser or mobile address. Unless you choose to identify yourself to UberMedia (through an account or otherwise), you will remain anonymous to us. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies. However, if you do so, certain features may not work.
  * _Web beacon:_ A web beacon is an electronic image on a web page that recognizes certain types of information on your computer when you visit that particular web page.
  * _IP address:_ An Internet Protocol Address is a numerical label that is assigned to each computer on the Internet.
  * _Referring website address:_ A referring website address identifies the address of the webpage you were on previously, before you came to the Sites.
  * _Browser:_ A browser is a software application used for retrieving, presenting and traversing information resources on the World Wide Web.

UberMedia respects the rights of copyright and trademark owners. UberMedia responds to clear notices of infringement of third party intellectual property rights in accord with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) for copyrights, and uses a similar process for trademark infringement claims.

**Copyright Infringement**

To notify us of alleged copyright infringement, you need to send us a written notice by mail or fax that includes all of the following:

  1. Identification of the copyrighted work you believe is being infringed. Please give us enough specific detail that we can find the work.
  2. Identification of the work you believe is infringing, with information that is reasonably sufficient for us to find it.
  3. Your address, phone number and, if applicable, email address.
  4. This statement: “I have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.”
  5. This statement: “The information in this notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, I am the copyright owner or am authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.”
  6. A physical or electronic signature of “a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the exclusive right that has allegedly been infringed.”

UberMedia will treat copyright infringement notices that meet these requirements in accord with the DMCA.

If we have taken down content that you believe should not have been removed, you can send us a written counter-notice by mail or fax that meets the DMCA requirements and we will follow the process set out in the DMCA. More information on the DMCA is available at http://copyright.gov.

**Trademark Infringement**

To notify us of a trademark infringement, please send us a notice that includes (a) the specific trademark you believe is being infringed, (b) detailed information about the trademark you believe is infringing and where you saw that infringing trademark on our site, (c) your name, address and email address, statements that are the equivalent to #4 and #5 above but as to the trademark instead of a copyright, (d) a physical or electronic signature meeting the requirements of information as for a copyright notice, plus the serial or registration number of the trademark if it has been registered.

**UberMedia’s Response**

We will respond to all infringement notices and comply with applicable law. As we say in our Universal Terms, we reserve the right to remove any content without prior notice and at our sole discretion. We also reserve the right to terminate a user’s account and/or access if the user is determined to be a repeat infringer.

**Where to Send Notices**

Please send infringement notices to:

Infringement Complaints  
UberMedia, Inc.  
130 West Union Street  
Pasadena, CA 91103

Email: [copyright@ubermedia.com](mailto:copyright@ubermedia.com)

Effective: March 5th, 2011
